# **SOKARI THANKGOD**

AHOADA TOWN, AHOADE EAST L.G.A., sokarithankgod2@gmail.com, 09053046284, 09035383250.

#### PROFILE

Creative developer with rapidly growing cognate experience in marketing and product design, web design and development. Possess a keen desire to create dynamic and intuitive marketing strategy, web features to simplify navigation for end users. Enthusiastic to join your company as a marketer and a front-end developer, using my knowledge of modern marketing and modern libraries and frameworks to help grow your company's offline and online presence and increase traffic and revenue.

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

• Frontend developer & Online Marketer at Frontend mentorship, remote.

December 2021 - Present

Creating and selling a paid online platform where Front-end newbies can get the appropriate knowledge about frontend development.

Product Marketer at Neo-Life

June 2020 - September 2021

Selling and distributing foreign health care medications (drugs), wholesales and retails.

## EDUCATION

 Higher National Diploma (in-view), Kenule Beeson Saro-wawa polytechnic, Bori November 2021 - Present Attaining a Higher National Diploma in Computer science.

 National Diploma, Kenule Beeson Saro-wawa polytechnic, Bori November 2018 – March 2021
Attained a National Diploma in Computer science.

## SKILLS

- Online & Offline Marketing
- Presentation
- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- Git
- Reactjs

#### HOBBIES

Due to my enduring passion for marketing and software development, I enjoy expanding my knowledge of various Marketing courses and Computer program that I can use to further my career in the industry. I also enjoy playing a variety of games.